# 哈喽大家好
Hello everybody
# 今天我们又不用做菜了
Today we are not gonna cook
# 今天让我伯爷留了一笼肥肠
My uncle left me some pork intestine
# 跟大家分享一个小技巧
I am gonna share a pro tip with you guys
# 就是说我们前段时间
Last time we
# 做了一个菜叫做“干煸肥肠”
cooked a dish called “Fried pork intestine”
# 当时（视频）里面我是说光滑这一面是
In that video, I said the smooth side is to
# 装大便的
hold the stool
# 装粪便的
hold the feces
# 有的粉丝他有点质疑
Some fans doubt it
# 他说带油这边是接触粪便的一面
They said the side with oil is the side that contacts the feces
# 现在我就请伯爷做了三四十年的杀猪匠
Now I invite my uncle, who has been pig butcher for almost forty years
# 来跟你们分享一下这个小技巧
to share this tip
# 四伯爷为什么它要翻过来安
Why is it turned inside out, uncle?
# 它不翻过来里面这个粪便怎么洗得干净安
You cannot clean the feces inside thoroughly unless turned inside out
# 你咋个整来吃安
If you cannot clean it, you cannot eat it
# 现在有个问题是这样的
Now we have a question
# 这个肥肠出来的时候
When the pork intestine comes out
# 到底是光滑这面接触粪便的
whether the smooth side or the
# 还是说带油的一面是解除粪便的
oily side is the side that contacts the feces
# 光滑一面（接触）带粪便的
The smooth side contacts feces
# 里面那个角油如果带粪便你洗都洗不干净哒
If the oily side contacts feces, you are not able to clean it up
# 现在我们看到这个肥肠就是光光滑滑的
Now we see the pork intestine is very smooth
# 其实这一面已经被翻过来了
Actually, the inside is already flipped over
# 翻过来了其实里面有一些油
There is still some oil inside
# 它里面那一层油的话是那个肠连接在一起的时候粘连住的油
The oil inside is to connect the intestine together
# 那个咋子说安 角油
What’s that called?
# 叫角油
Called “Jiao you”
# 里面那个角油
The “Jiao you” inside
# 你看嘛翻过来你看嘛
You can see
# 这边就（全）是角油
The “Jiao you” is all over inside
# （如果）粪便装在里面看你怎么洗得干净
If the feces are inside, how can you wash them clean?
# 必须翻过来
So, you must turn the inside out
# 开始在猪肚皮里面的时候它是这样的
When it was still inside the pig it’s like this
# 这里面就是装的粪便
The feces were held inside
# 我们这样把它翻过来过后
After we turn the inside out
# 那个粪便粘在上面用水一洗就洗干净了
The feces sticking to it can be easily cleaned by water
# 还有一个就是这个肥肠现在是经过处理的
One more thing is that, this intestine is already processed
# 其实这样子看起来是一条一条的
They look like in strips now
# 但是它在猪的肚子里面的时候它不是一条的
But when they were in the pig
# 它是盘起来的
they were stacked together
# 它盘起来粘连的那个油（角油）
The oil (“Jiao you”) that helps stacking
# 里面的那个油就是粘连肥肠的那个油
is the oil that connects the intestine together
# 现在的话它是一条一条的
Now it is in strips
# 处理好了就是这样子卖
That’s how it’s sold
# 是不是 是啊
Is it?
# 它就是弄个子的撒
That’s how it works
# 你看 到市场上你去看那些屠夫些卖肉
The butchers also deal like this in market
# 这个大肠就是弄个子翻起的 翻来卖起的
Pork intestine needs to be turned over to sell
# 你那样翻转来 全是角油 乱翻翻的
If you flip in that way, the “Jiao you” will be all over and in a mess
# 人家看着（不好看） 哪个买你的安
Customers won’t buy it
# 所以我们现在得出一个结论
Now we come to a conclusion
# 就是肥肠光滑这一面是接触粪便这一面
The smooth side of the pork intestine is the one that contacts the feces
# 有油的那一面它是外面的那一面
The side with oil is the outside
# 有油它用那个油粘连住这个肠子
The oil is to connect the intestine together
# 就是说不是一条一条的
That means it was not in strips
# 它是盘起来的肠子
The intestine was stacked together
# 好了 本期视频就到这里吧
Okay, it’s the end of this video
# 这个问题终于搞清楚了
Now we have figured it out
# 光滑一面是接触粪便的
The smooth side is in contact with feces
# 不光滑带油的那一面是在外面的 对吧
The greasy side is on the outside, right?
# 嗯
Right
# 在肚子头就是外面的
When inside belly, the greasy side of intestine is the outside
# 拿出来我们翻过来
We take it out, and turn the inside out
# 把那个粪便那方翻过来是光滑那方是装粪便的
Turn the smooth side out, which is the side that holds feces
# 里头就是角油
Inside is “Jiao you”
# 嗯
Yep
# 就是弄个做起的
That’s it